(Life Is Full of Variables)
Nice to see you, everyone.
- MINHO. - Yes.
So our country actually acknowledged you...
as the passionate and charismatic athlete.
- What? - What's this about?
- It's a huge honor for me. - Yes.
I was appointed the honorary ambassador of KSOC.
What?
I'll be their honorary ambassador for two years.
("MINHO Gets Appointed Honorary Ambassador")
("MINHO, the New Face of KSOC")
You're the perfect person for it.
- Right. - Yes.
- Only you can pull that off. - Exactly.
- Yes. - What a positive appointment.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- They picked the right guy. - With this momentum,
- you'll exercise even more. - Yes.
By the way, I really wanted to see you.
- Me? - Why?
Yes. You guys had the race last time I was here.
- Oh, the race of the century? - I see. Right.
You guys teased him a lot.
It's totally going to work.
(He went up against CODE KUNST in a soccer match...)
(and lost.)
(MINHO, you were supposed to give it a curve.)
(And you were supposed to kick it with the back of your foot.)
(Getting lectured from the two upset him more than the result.)
(Gosh, you're frustrating.)
(He kindly demonstrated for MINHO out of frustration.)
(This is how you do it.)
(MINHO, I ought to help you polish your skills.)
Here's what I really loved about MINHO.
After Hyun Moo and I gave you a few tips on playing soccer,
- Yes. - I...
- watched him play soccer. - Okay.
Your movements definitely got smoother.
- So... - We had an influence on him.
- Let me explain. - Our theoretical knowledge is good.
- We'll have a sports day. - Yes.
- You must come as Iron Man. - Yes.
- It won't be complete without you. - Right.
And we'll be teamed up together.
- Come on. Let's do a handshake. - He's pulling away.
(In a hurry)
- Hold on. Are there already teams? - Wait. What are the teams?
Innocent Moo and Ku Sports Day...
- is the name. - Yes.
- There are Team Moo and Team Ku. - Team Moo and Team Ku.
- Team Moo and Team Ku. - Team Moo...
And I want you on my team, MINHO.
- Are you recruiting him now? - Oh, my.
This is the recruiting battle.
You know what? I taught you a few tips and so on.
If MINHO joins your team, I'll follow him.
- Yes. - This is nice.
- I'm the team captain. - No.
We should all be on Team MINHO.
- Yes, let's be on Team MINHO. Yes. - We'll be on Team MINHO.
The rest of the guests will join Team Hyun Moo.
Kian84, I want you on my team.
- Me? - I need at least you.
I don't want to join neither.
- Join him. - Come on.
- My gosh, seriously. - You're being mean.
Just pretend that there are no team captains.
In the end, you'll have to play rock-paper-scissors...
- and pick. - Right.
- I thought you were confident. - Yes. Of course.
Rock-paper-scissors.
MINHO.
(He's unstoppable.)
- Here's what's important. - Yes.
You guys don't know what kind of sport we'll play.
- We're working on that now. - I see.
Are there prizes too?
- There are. - Really?
Yes, I'll spend some money.
(Spoken like old money)
- Chairman Jun. - This will motivate us to play.
- We'll be playing real sports. - My gosh.
- I love that. - This is great.
I'll come up with the sports day...
that will satisfy even the honorary ambassador.
- I'll be looking forward to it. - Yes.
(Being Handsome Is Torture)
- "Being Handsome Is Torture?" - What's that?
"Being Handsome Is Torture."
(Sung Hwan is trudging along in the pouring rain.)
Look at your knee.
It still hasn't healed.
That was after the race with Hyun Moo.
- It still hasn't healed? - No.
It's a different wound.
I was practicing action scenes and then hurt myself.
Did the race affect your training?
I hurt my left knee then, but that's my right knee.
Both of your knees were destroyed.
They were totally destroyed.
- The injury is all over his body. - Both of them were injured.
Both of his legs were injured.
Sung Hwan, you should sit out the sports day.
- Right. - Yes.
How can you play with injured legs?
- I'm doing physical therapy now. - Sung Hwan.
Let's just do the fan dance.
- Yes. Let's do that. - What race? Seriously.
(Pouring)
My gosh, why is it pouring today?
(Shaking)
Your shoulders are so broad that one of your shoulders got wet.
I loved how you put it.
(Satisfied)
(He arrives at a place with a wet shoulder.)
(Checking his face)
My goodness.
- How handsome. - Yes.
What a handsome face from every angle.
- This is driving me crazy. - What?
- Is it about hair loss? - No.
- Physical therapy for your knees? - No.
(Laughing)
Let's go.
Going up.
Where are you going?
(Exhaling)
The doors are opening.
(He arrives while feeling anxious.)
- It must be a dermatology clinic. - Right.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's a clinic. - Hello.
(Pressing)
I've registered you. You can wait for a bit.
Okay.
(He's registered into a mysterious system.)
(Chuckling)
(Hold on.)
This looks familiar.
- What? - This...
(This looks familiar for some reason.)
(It was seen at Moomoo's house.)
"The Martian."
(Abundant nature)
I told you it'd be at a subway station...
- or a dermatology clinic. - My gosh.
- It's the same thing. - It looks exactly the same.
They must be managed by the same agency.
- I guess we use the same agency. - Right.
- The same agency? - That's not important.
No one has that at home.
- Who would have that at their home? - Exactly.
When I saw it, I thought I was at your house.
Right. It's the interior design of a lobby.
Hyun Moo likes this kind of thing.
Gosh, he and I can't ever mix.
You just don't mix well.
(He sits down while feeling Moomoo's energy.)
All right.
(Let's see.)
(He's checking his face again.)
How unfortunate.
I should have come sooner. But I've been putting it off.
I came to a hospital because of vitiligo.
- Really? - I see.
The discoloration was getting wider.
(He always applied sunscreen...)
(that turned his skin whiter than that of Kkotbun.)
(There was a reason behind that.)
(A few years ago, I filmed a movie in Kazakhstan with Ju Seung.)
(Afterward, his vitiligo has gotten worse.)
- Because of the sun. - Yes.
(My doctor told me to apply a lot of sunscreen.)
(He always relied on sunscreen.)
- You began applying it generously. - Yes.
Actually, I apply a lot more when I go out.
- You should. - I apply it on my neck too.
But I went to the beach this summer.
Only the discolored patches didn't get tanned.
- So it looks worse now. - Gosh.
- That must be so stressful. - It's not like...
you can cover up the patches.
You're an actor too.
- Right. It must be... - Your face is on TV all the time.
- so stressful. - This must be stressful.
When I'm on TV, the viewers can't see the patches...
because I cover them up with makeup.
- I'm not wearing any makeup now. - My gosh.
- I'm not sure if you can see them. - Right.
You can see them on my eyebrow,
- My gosh. - nose, and mouth.
- Oh, no. - They're all over my face.
I'm getting more patches now.
It's not that I don't have any eyebrows.
It got decolored and became white.
- I see. - That's pretty serious.
All of the facial hair will turn white.
- Really? - I see.
It sounds like a serious condition.
I got tested in May.
The doctor was surprised...
and brought in the nurses and the chief nurse.
Afterward, this condition began to stress me.
I was wondering if this condition could improve.
That's why I'm here on my day off.
- You must get treated for it. - Sung Hwan, is it possible?
Can it improve with the right treatment?
Actually, the thing with vitiligo is...
- there's no cure. - Right. It will be difficult.
If you don't take precautions, the patches could widen again?
That's why I've been going to the clinic often.
- To prevent them from getting big? - I see.
(This isn't his first time here.)
Gosh, why am I nervous?
Sung Hwan, let's get you prepared.
Okay.
(Getting up)
Please put on the gown...
- and change your shoes. - Okay.
(Men's Dressing Room)
(He enters the washroom after getting changed.)
(He's ready to wash his face after putting on a cute headband.)
That's quite a face.
(I know it's my face and all, but that's quite a face.)
Gosh, it makes me shy to wash my face there.
- You have to, though. - Yes.
Because the doctor must see your bare face to diagnose?
- They tell you to wash your face. - You must wash up completely.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
That's my habit.
(Glancing)
- Oh, no. - My gosh.
(He realizes something went wrong.)
(He quickly tries to wipe them with his hand.)
(A quick glance)
I cleaned it.
(He thoroughly wipes the mirror.)
You can just wipe it.
My gosh.
(I forgot to wash my face. Only the mirror is clean.)
(Thoroughly washing)
You took a shower in there.
(He dries the mirror at the end.)
Okay.
All done.
(His face and mirror are both clean.)
- Are you done? - Yes.
- Then... - Okay.
You'll use Meta-Vu, the skin analyzer.
Put your head in all the way. Great.
- With that device, you can see... - It captures everything?
All the discolored patches.
- I didn't know about this device. - Yes.
- You look like a baby again. - My gosh.
- You're a baby. - Let's skip this part.
- He looks like a baby. - Yes.
- Totally. - He's a new infant.
This is "2001: A Space Odyssey."
(He seems excited as if he were getting on a spaceship.)
He looks like a guy from the future.
I'll pull this down.
Okay.
Maintain this pose.
- Follow the audio directions. - Okay.
The scanning will begin now.
Please open your eyes.
(Opening wide)
- I see. It scans your whole face. - Please open your eyes.
They're open.
(Gleaming eyes)
Close your eyes.
The scanning is over.
It's over now.
Come this way.
I hope I don't get any bad news.
You must be so nervous.
- All right. - Have you been well?
Yes. I've been well.
- My gosh. - You haven't been here.
- Well, my face... - Yes.
This part gets so dry.
- The part with the patches. - Right.
- Yes. - Right.
- As you can see. - Yes.
So tell me. How am I doing?
Let me explain.
Because of the immune reaction, the pigment cells are destroyed.
So parts of your face are turning white.
That's why the texture of your skin...
- is bound to get worse. - I see.
Let me show you.
(I'll explain more with the scans you just took.)
- Gosh. What is this? - See my face on the far right.
You look like a Na'vi from "Avatar" in the last picture.
My skin condition is one thing.
But I look so ugly in the picture.
It's impossible to look good in that photo.
- Right. No one can look good. - You're supposed to look like that.
- Right? - You know what?
Even MINHO can't survive in the picture.
- It's how it is with everyone. - Everyone looks ugly in that.
- It shows all of your pores. - Right, every one of them.
- These are the scans from today. - Yes.
If you only look at these scans,
you might not know what you're looking at.
Let me compare them...
- with the scans from last time. - Yes.
These were taken in May.
- In May? - And they were taken today.
As you can see...
Did he get more patches?
- the discolored patches... - Yes.
- actually have gotten better. - Gosh, his face is moving.
That was the best facial expression...
- you could do, right? - Yes, it was.
I look like that when I open my eyes.
You've been wearing sunscreen diligently.
You've been taking care of your skin well. As for the patches,
they actually look like they've gotten better.
But when we check the UV scans,
- well, you can see that... - They've gotten bigger.
They've gotten wider.
- They've gotten wider? - Yes.
This patch is spreading upward.
- Oh, no. - So...
Yes, the doctor is right.
My goodness. I was so shocked.
During the last three months, I've gained a lot of weight too.
Just like my weight gain,
- the patches have stretched. - Right.
- Of course. - Your body stretched.
Here's the thing about vitiligo.
It's a refractory condition.
I can't guarantee...
that I can cure this condition. I can't promise you that.
Receiving treatment regularly could be helpful.
You've been applying sunscreen diligently.
The most important step is...
- cleansing. - Cleansing.
You must clean it off completely.
Sunscreen can be quite irritating to our skin.
No matter how tired and exhausted you are,
- I always wash my face. - you must always clean it off.
- Hydrating your skin is important. - Okay.
- Since I'm here, - Yes.
- give me a good treatment. - Okay.
Could you apply a thicker layer of the numbing cream...
than last time?
- A thicker layer? - My gosh. It hurts a lot.
It hurt a lot last time.
- Here's why. - Like we're layering a cake?
- That would be nice. - Sure. I got it.
- Thank you. - My nurses will help you.
- Okay. - Cake up the numbing cream.
- Yes. - Cake up the numbing cream?
Please lie down. I'll put on the numbing cream.
Thank you.
I'll put on a thicker layer.
- We'll wait longer for anesthesia. - Okay.
Please put on a thicker layer.
- Sure. It's cold. - Okay.
The treatment covers my entire face.
- Please spread it thoroughly. - Okay.
It hurts a lot.
I don't have to do anything special today, right?
My gosh. The pain was unbearable for me.
They're really caking it up on him.
That means you're bread.
(Oh, no!)
Given how wide it is, he's sulbbang.
(Given how wide it is, he's sulbbang.)
People steam bread like that in cauldrons for village festivals.
(The whipped sulbbang for the festival is ready!)
Given how thick it is, I won't feel any pain today. Right?
You should be good.
It hurt a lot last time.
This hurts a lot.
- It was so painful for you. - It was really painful.
We'll give the cream 20 minutes...
- to activate. - Okay.
(Waiting 20 minutes to soften the pain)
(Groaning)
- What's this sound? - My gosh. He's groaning.
(Snoring)
Did you fall asleep?
(Snoring loudly)
(Strained snoring)
I guess you sleep well at clinics and hospitals.
I couldn't sleep the night before at the thought of going there.
(It's been 20 minutes.)
(Exhaling)
My gosh.
The sulbbang is getting steamed.
That's when you need to remove the lid.
The steam will come out then.
(Sulbbang)
(The whipped sulbbang is steamed nicely.)
(Carefully tapping)
Can I wipe off the numbing cream?
Yes.
- I... - I guess you were so relaxed.
I'm sorry. I feel so refreshed.
I slept like a lamb, right?
It seemed you were sleeping well.
Is that so?
- This is cold. - Okay.
- If my skin is under anesthesia, - Yes.
How come I can feel the cold towel?
Do you think you can feel everything?
Is it because your skin is thick?
And I get scared easily.
(Pinching)
(I'll be okay today. Right?)
I'll walk you to the operating room.
(He's fully ready.)
- You can turn left. - Hello.
- Hello. - This way, please.
- That's scary. - Please lie down...
- with your head facing up. - Okay.
- Are you feeling all right? - Yes.
See if you can endure...
- the pain better than before. - Okay.
If it hurts a lot,
- squeeze the doll. - You need that doll.
I'll stimulate your skin with the high-frequency device.
These are called autologous exosomes.
I'll spread them out, so your skin can absorb them.
That will be our goal.
Anyway, help me improve my vitiligo.
If it's too hot, let me know.
- All right. I'll begin. - What's this?
(The procedure begins.)
My gosh. That must hurt.
(Stimulating the skin with high frequency)
(Flinching)
- My gosh. - Oh, no.
(The pain comes through anesthesia.)
- It hurts that much? - It hurts a lot.
- I can feel the pain. - Even with the numbing cream?
My gosh. Seriously.
I'm sweating just by watching this clip.
(He's done this many times, but he can't get used to this.)
- Gosh, it must hurt a lot. - It must hurt.
- Does it help them from spreading? - Yes.
Hold on. Seriously.
- Those spots... - Wait.
- If you move, it's more dangerous. - My gosh.
- Sorry. - We're not done yet.
Honestly, I thought about living with vitiligo.
Calling it an incurable disease sounds a bit dramatic.
But it is true it's very difficult to cure this condition.
Here's what I want the most.
I don't want the patches to show.
I'm trying to stay positive.
Actually, the truth is...
I'm a lot more stressed about this than I'm sharing.
This looks so painful.
It'd be better if his condition could improve.
(He can bear with any pain if his condition can improve.)
The ultrasonic waves are coming out.
- You'll hear some whizzing sounds. - Okay.
- So bear with the sounds. - Okay.
If it was on your arm,
- you would've lived with it. - Right.
But this must be harder on you since it's on your face.
We'll move you to the treatment room for the rest.
It took over an hour.
Good job.
- That must've been tough. - It must've been so tough.
I must get the treatment regularly to see any improvement.
I'll apply soothing face cream...
that helps your skin regenerate and stay protected.
Okay. Thank you.
- That's the coolest. - That's really cool.
Gosh, I want to do that again.
It's really cold.
Yes.
(Covering)
She covered up his mouth.
You'll stay like this for ten minutes.
Okay.
It's going up. His mouth is twitching.
(He falls asleep right after the draining procedure.)
He's snoring again?
He falls asleep so fast.
It's always embarrassing because I snore wherever I sleep.
Sleeping on the airplane must be uncomfortable for you.
I always feel bad.
When I sleep,
I can feel that I'm snoring.
- You can feel it too, right? - I can.
People think it's the sound of the engine.
The studio even woke me up.
The studio?
- The stewardess... - The studio?
- Who's this studio? - The studio?
(Oh, Sung Hwan...)
(Snoring)
Let me remove this.
(His face is still red.)
- Here it is. - Okay.
(His skin still needs soothing.)
(Gentle)
- I guess there's a laser treatment. - Yes, it's a laser treatment.
(Come on, Sung Hwan.)
- You look better like this. - They look great on you.
You look better like this.
They're covering you up with a lot of stuff.
They're using a lot of cutting-edge devices.
What?
(We can't hold back our laughter anymore.)
- That looks even more bizarre. - My gosh.
(Shocked)
- He was in "Toy Story." - This is...
- He looks like a cartoon character. - Look!
It looks like he's in space too.
An alien is here to conquer our planet.
To conquer our planet?
(The conqueror from space is coming after our planet.)
Why are you smiling?
But he looks like a kind alien.
- Set that as your profile picture. - Are you all right?
Yes.
The alien is smiling subtly.
- It's like he's dreaming... - He looks like an alien.
Of conquering our planet...
- on the spaceship. - Yes.
(Comfortable)
I'll remove this.
She didn't laugh at him, though.
I go there often.
(She applies sunscreen on him as if she had done this many times.)
Did it stop raining?
They apply a lot of sunscreen after the treatment.
- You're all set. - Thank you.
- Good job hanging in there. - Thank you.
- That must've been tough. - Okay.
- I had been putting it off. - Okay. Thank you.
So when I was there, I felt relieved.
I'm glad you went.
- Thank you. Have a good day. - Thank you.
Thanks. Bye.
(He strides out of the pharmacy.)
There it is.
(He called a taxi in advance.)
(Exhausted from the surgery...)
- Hello. - Hello.
(He quickly heads out.)
(Looking full of worry)
I was so stressed.
When you go to clinics for health reasons,
- those visits feel like homework. - And...
(Samgakji Station)
I wonder where he's going next.
He'll probably eat something.
Right. For sure.
Since he has vitiligo, he'll get a dish starting with V.
- That will be his excuse. - Right.
It's raining.
Have a good day.
(He arrives at a place after the treatment.)
Gosh, this is nice.
- He's in Itaewon. - I'm hungry.
(Itaewon)
I have an English name, Marcus.
I was exposed to the American culture...
ever since I was a kid.
In 2003, I lived in Itaewon...
for a year.
Really?
Yes. I lived at my friend's house...
when I performed in children's plays.
I lived with him for a year.
("The Tale of Sim Cheong")
From 2010 to 2015,
I used to come here on Thursday, Friday, and Saturday.
That's how much I love the culture in Itaewon.
I would say Itaewon is my fifth hometown.
You have a lot of hometowns.
(You have five hometowns?)
My gosh, it smells good.
Excuse me.
(He starts speaking in English now that he's in his hometown.)
(He naturally heads into a burger place.)
- You love burgers. - I love burgers.
- That's Marcus indeed. - Hello.
Yes.
(Exuding the American vibe)
As for the restaurant I visited today,
that's my go-to spot when I'm stressed.
It's my soulmate that can comfort me.
It was the dish I wanted the most when I was stressed.
I hated how painful it was. So I went...
to an authentic American place.
I went to have an authentic American burger.
You need a reward.
I'm salivating.
(He's here for a comforting meal after a hard day.)
- Hello. - My gosh.
The Korean workers aren't here today.
(He hesitates after seeing a non-Korean worker.)
- Hi. - Hi.
Well, the menu is...
only at the kiosk?
Yes. You have to order from there.
The best burger is the deluxe burger.
So you can try that one.
- Yes. - Okay. Thank you.
I don't know what she said.
He thanked her when he didn't understand her.
He cut her off before she could speak more.
Right. "Thank you."
A cheeseburger.
As long as you don't eat any fritters...
- Right. Just don't eat the fries. - Seriously. Yes.
- It's the perfect meal. - It's great.
- You're spot on. - It's the perfect meal.
He's getting three burgers.
But getting three would be a different story.
What? What's this?
- He ordered three burgers. - Gosh.
- And he ordered sugar-free Coke. - He ordered three burgers.
- Their burgers are great. - Just eat the fries...
and have only one burger.
No. I can't do that. My conscience won't allow it.
Three?
(He orders three burgers which are perfectly balanced.)
- Excuse me. - Yes.
Romaine and tomatoes. Outside.
- Okay. - Okay?
- Ippai sauce... - Yes.
- Many... - What?
(Ippai? Many?)
(He perfectly speaks 2 languages.)
"Can you add a lot of it?"
(He just wanted a lot of sauce.)
- Yes. - Ippai sauce...
- Many... Dip a lot. Okay? - You want a lot of sauce?
- Okay. Thank you. - All right.
(He customized his order by using 3 languages.)
(It will wash away the pain from the treatment.)
It's so greasy.
(Looking glossy)
The smell is driving me crazy.
(He gets up as the smell makes it impossible to stay still.)
Is my order not ready yet?
- Excuse me. - Yes.
You speak Korean and English?
I mean, you speak Korean?
- Yes, I can speak Korean. - You can?
Her pronunciation is better than yours.
- Her pronunciation is better. - My gosh.
- This is the deluxe burger. - The deluxe burger.
This one is the cheeseburger. And this is the chicken burger.
- As you requested, - I see.
I didn't add any lettuce or tomatoes.
What? You speak such good Korean!
She thought I was one of the foreign customers.
So she didn't speak Korean to me.
- They get foreign customers too. - She thought you were Marcus.
Gosh, this is so embarrassing.
(He quickly goes to his table.)
(The trio of burgers chosen by Marcus)
(He solemnly puts on plastic gloves.)
Calm down.
- Calm down. - They always have black pepper.
- You must sprinkle some pepper. - Oh, my.
- There you go. - Hey.
- Gosh. - Black pepper.
He's sprinkling it on everything. Look at him coughing.
Of course, it makes me cough.
This is a solemn moment.
(Pressing)
Why are you pressing it?
So I can get a nice bite of it.
(He presses down on the burger and then takes a bite.)
(Humming)
Gosh, that's really tasty.
(He keeps on biting into his comfort food.)
Gosh, this is crazy.
(It's washing away all of my stress.)
(Approving)
He eats so neatly.
Nothing is spilling over.
Look at that. How neat was that?
He finished that in 3 to 4 bites.
He finished that so quickly like it was a macaron.
- He really eats it like a macaron. - Seriously.
(Given the speed, he's having his second macaron.)
(He's utterly captivated by his favorite food.)
- I think you're eating too fast. - Right.
- I'm trying to fix that. - Right. You need to chew more.
Right.
You're eating like it's a food competition.
Is it because you felt empty inside? What were you feeling?
That day, I just wanted to gorge on my favorite food...
because I was so stressed.
I don't eat when I'm really full...
because I wouldn't feel good.
- It's the same with everyone. - Really?
- I... - Everyone stops eating then.
(That's normal.)
(Since he's not full, he grabs the last burger.)
You're eating all three burgers without a sip of the Coke.
There's a moment when I drink Coke.
I drink it when I feel full.
You don't drink it throughout the meal.
- I guess he has his own rule. - I do.
(A solo performance of the burger without the Coke)
- Did he finish all three? - Gosh, that was so fast.
- He's drinking it now. - I think it only took five minutes.
(He finally gulps down the Coke.)
And I must drink soda until my throat hurts.
After that, he always says...
- he has reflux esophagitis. - Right.
I still take a lot of medicine.
(But he washes down his stress.)
I'm on a diet now.
So I only ate about 70 percent of my usual meal.
I need to get in shape for work now.
Last time, I raced against Hyun Moo. Due to bad blood circulation,
I got a leg cramp, so I lost.
That's why I'm watching my figure now.
People might think that we competed in the Olympics.
It wasn't grand or anything.
We just ran for a bit in front of the MBC building.
How could you get a leg cramp and blame your blood circulation?
I didn't eat the fries. I'm on a diet.
If I keep this diet up,
I'll lose 10kg after 3 weeks.
I'm sure of it.
Gosh, that was good.
I should go and have some desserts.
Thank you.
- You're going for sweets. - Sweets.
- Itaewon has many dessert shops. - Thank you.
There are good dessert shops in Itaewon.
What a nice meal.
(Just then as the sky clears up, his pain eases too.)
My gosh. This is nice.
You look so happy.
- How cute. - How adorable.
- A girl? - What?
- A girl? - Yes.
Yes. My gosh.
Her eyes are so beautiful.
- I see. - Yes.
- Where are you from? - Spain.
- Spain. - Yes, Spain.
You... Can Korean speak English?
What's he saying?
- "Can Korean speak English?" - Okay.
"You Korean can speak English."
Bye.
- Bye. - Bye.
English is all about confidence.
You just have to go for it.
- You need to keep practicing. - Right.
I can make small talk with people now.
(He's confidently roaming around his 5th hometown.)
Gosh, America.
I wonder what he's going to eat.
Where's he going?
- My gosh. - Beyran.
- Oh, right. Yes! - Beyran.
(Beyran?)
You know what?
(The Palm Oil Family had beyran during their seminar in Turkiye.)
This is the ox bone broth.
(They inhaled it as it was spicy ox bone broth.)
(It would be a hit in Korea.)
(They were amazed by beyran.)
You know what? Let me explain what happened.
- What? - You know,
- I have the Turkish friend. - Yes.
- The one whose last name is Im. - Yes.
I asked her how come we couldn't get beyran...
when we could get a lot of Turkish dishes in Korea.
The owner of the Turkish restaurant...
saw our episode in Turkiye...
and added beyran to the menu.
- And that's the restaurant? - Yes, it is.
What a surprise. This is so touching.
Kaymak.
(Staring)
Kebab?
- Hey. - Ice cream?
Can you speak Korean?
Yes, I can. A bit.
- A bit. - Yes, I can.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
- I'm Mr. Ku. - I'm Harun.
- Harin? - Harun.
- Harun. Nice to meet you. - Yes.
Nice to meet you. Thank you so much.
- One ice cream. - Would you like some ice cream?
Okay. Turkish ice cream is tasty.
My gosh.
By the way, his skills are quite advanced.
Okay.
(Slow)
- Gosh. - Ice cream.
- Enjoy. - What?
Okay.
- It's tasty. - That was new.
- You caught him off guard. - Sung Hwan.
(He still ate the cone.)
(He gets another cone.)
Enjoy. I'll give you a lot. Wait.
Wait.
(Crunchy)
You're going to ruin his business!
But the cones were so savory.
They were so savory. I kept on eating them.
How many cones will you eat?
When he grabs it, he puts it in his mouth.
- That's what babies do. - I didn't want him to take it away.
- Oh, you want me to wait? Sorry. - Yes.
It's okay.
Here you go.
- Enjoy. - Gosh, this is tough.
(Not to lose any more cones, he gives it to Sung Hwan.)
- Wait. - He didn't tease Sung Hwan.
- Thank you. - He didn't tease you a lot.
- Right. - He must've been angry.
(Humming)
- You're good with your hands. - Yes.
(Taking a bite)
(His ice cream is great.)
It was so chewy.
(Finishing it in an instant)
- I'll come back. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(Enjoying a familiar flavor from the 5th hometown)
Excuse me.
(He walks around Itaewon after enjoying his ice cream.)
I haven't been here in a while.
I can smell the furniture.
- Itaewon is famous for furniture. - Yes.
It was nice to be out on the street of Itaewon after a while.
It's nice to be back after a while.
(Glancing)
Gosh, look at this place. This place looks hip. What is it?
(Peeking)
This place looks hip.
Are you going to buy clothes?
Are you going to buy an outfit? It's been a while.
- Hello. You're open, right? Okay. - Yes.
Hello.
I love how it smells here. It smells like Itaewon.
- That looks... - So you do buy clothes.
I've never seen you shop for clothes.
This is interesting.
(A clothing store with the full-on American vibe)
This kind of style looks good on you.
- Workwear looks good on you. - Workwear.
- Sung Hwan has broad shoulders. - Yes.
- He's got a nice build. - Yes, he has a great build.
You always say the sweetest things.
I rarely went clothes shopping before...
because I couldn't buy clothes from department stores.
Clothes from there don't fit you?
When I was young, I really wanted to wear 29513 STORM.
- I haven't heard that in a while. - But...
(The fitted style stood out in STORM's clothes.)
(Seo Taiji, the president of the 90s, led the STORM trend.)
(It was the symbol of being hip among young people...)
(such as Song Seung Heon and So Ji Sub.)
Nothing fits me.
So I rarely go shopping.
The outfits in my dressing room...
probably don't add up to 30.
I have some pants and katamaes.
Katamae?
- Katamae? - They don't add up to 30.
(Regardless of when, where, or what he did, )
(he always wore the navy collar T-shirt.)
He always wore that shirt.
- My gosh. - I also have a lot of that shirt.
The green T-shirt.
- Yes. - That's right.
- He always wore the green T-shirt. - Yes.
People like me have clear fashion styles.
It's like Hollywood stars coming out of their houses...
without dressing up.
We wear outfits...
those Hollywood stars would wear in the paparazzi photos.
Athletic clothes, you know?
- Like that. - I see.
- Timothee Chalamet. - My gosh.
I wear a plain collar T-shirt...
- and a jacket. - Gosh. No!
- Marcus Ku. - Marcus Ku.
Just like Hollywood stars.
Actually, the photos are aligned at their shoes.
- Darn it. - That makes him look shorter.
- Hey. KEY. - Nothing gets past you.
Nothing gets past you.
- You... - You're the meanest.
Sung Hwan, you have the best shoulders.
You have the broadest shoulders.
- Make your shoulders shine. - Gosh.
So there's a clear fashion style I like.
That includes glasses.
- Looking hip effortlessly. - I have my own style.
You would actually look cool when you dress up.
Yes.
You have a lot of cute hats.
Are they from the US?
- No, we designed and made them. - You...
- Really? - Yes.
They look good.
Is there...
a katamae you would like to recommend?
- Katamae. - Katamae.
Ippai katamaes, please.
Then what do you call that?
- Jackets. - Jackets.
- This would look great on you. - That's cute.
Nice.
Workwear looks great on people with a nice build.
It would look great on them.
- Gosh, you have a big build. - I...
(Gosh, you have a big build.)
I... Gosh, this is too tight.
It's too tight.
You're really big.
The jacket will rip in the underarms.
The employee was startled too.
(Flustered)
A bigger size...
Jang Woo and I won't be able to come here.
Why do you keep bringing up Jang Woo?
Jang Woo is the only one with a similar build.
Why do you and Jang Woo like green?
- It's because... - Okay.
- we have a big belly. - Okay.
Black is nice, but it can be too dreary.
- Green is just right. - Is green just right?
Red stands out too much.
- Seriously, his shoulders... - They're unbelievable.
It's not just his shoulders.
- His back is broad too. - That's right.
You didn't get a big build by working out, right?
- No. I've always had a big build. - He was born with it.
You'll do really well in the US.
Among the stores in Itaewon, that one sells clothes that are...
- more fitted. - Slim clothes.
But small clothes are pretty.
You'll be able to wear all the pretty clothes.
The pant legs are too long for me.
- You'll still be able to wear them. - I need to cut off the pant legs.
That's better...
- because I can't wear them at all. - Really?
Why did you make them so small in Itaewon?
- The store? - No, the size of the clothes.
- The size of the clothes. - "The store?"
I'm sure different people come.
These days...
This one is nice.
- It's nice. - It's pretty.
- Many foreigners come. - Is that so?
But more than I thought, you're...
- He's speechless. - I know.
I look a bit like ZO ZAZZ.
- ZO ZAZZ. - ZO ZAZZ.
ZO ZAZZ has a good style.
- He has a good style. - He's fashionable.
- He has a good style. - Yes.
While it's pretty, it isn't my style.
- Really? - It isn't your style.
With a green T-shirt underneath, you won't be able to see...
- the vibe. - This place is nice.
- Do you visit Itaewon often? - I was practically a fixture.
- Really? - "A fixture."
I haven't heard that term in a while.
This one... I can't wear it.
- Is it too small? - I can't wear it.
- Is it too tight? - It's too tight.
He's sweating.
I wanted to cut off my body.
(Sucking in his breath)
There are many pretty items.
(But the size is the issue.)
(Disappointed)
The size...
Do I need to search for 4XL?
- Even if it's big, the arm holes... - That's right.
- You'll be able to move in them. - I prefer comfortable clothes.
The size was the problem.
My shoulders have been broad since ninth grade.
- Were you in 9th grade then? - Between 8th and 9th grades.
You were like the school's boss.
Sung Hwan, you were so handsome.
During the break, I went to the US and my sister dyed my hair.
You look unrecognizable.
- You were so handsome. - He was a handsome man.
He was so cool.
(After the period of a cool 9th grader, )
(his shoulders became even broader.)
- He was different. - His shoulders were insane.
- Sung Hwan was the cute type. - He had a pretty face...
- and broad shoulders. - He was a handsome man.
Seriously.
How old were you then?
- I was past 20. - You were past 20.
(His shoulders have been extraordinary since the 20s.)
The wingspan is the distance from fingertip to fingertip.
That's right. His wingspan is so long.
My wingspan is 193cm.
But my height is 180cm.
On the other hand, my legs...
It's embarrassing, but my nickname is Dachshund.
I have the upper body of a person who is 193cm tall...
and the lower body of a person who is 160cm tall.
Finding the right-sized clothes has been hard since middle school.
Is he like a gorilla?
- Gorillas have a big upper body. - That's right.
Michael Phelps.
- Is Phelps like that? - Yes.
- He has short legs and long arms. - You know,
my legs are very short.
- They're very short. - They're very short.
- Is that all? - That's all.
- They might be similar to mine. - They're similar.
- Na Rae, your legs might be longer. - My legs aren't that short.
(The cute Na Rae-corgi and Marcus-hund)
- Gosh, this one... - It's bright.
This one...
If this one doesn't fit, I won't be able to wear anything.
- It's too small. - His arms won't go up.
- The sleeves are too short. - They're too short.
That store has many pretty clothes, but...
- You can't wear that. - You can't wear that.
I won't be able to buy clothes here.
(The style suits me, but the size doesn't.)
(This isn't easy.)
- I was disappointed. - Then 4XL...
I weigh about 112kg.
(He makes an honest confession.)
- Do you weigh 112kg now? - Yes.
- That's right. You were slim then. - That's right.
(He and Jang Woo entered the 108kg Alliance.)
(Then he gained weight and became the Sung Hwan everyone knows today.)
It's my goal to hit...
the weight of 95kg until the sports competition.
Sir, may I take off my T-shirt since there are...
- no other customers? - Go right ahead.
- I'll take it off carefully. - Okay.
- Make yourself comfortable. - Okay.
Still, other customers might enter.
- He took it off. - Look at his arms.
- Go with 4XL. - For fatties.
People like us...
That one looks nice.
- Not bad. - It isn't half bad.
(Finally!)
I have really long arms.
(Marcus-hund's long arms become a problem.)
It's too small.
I'm beginning to sweat.
I have really long arms.
Because of me, the employees had a hard time that day.
They tried to recommend me pretty clothes.
- You should focus on the size. - Then you'll find fitting clothes.
The size is the problem.
(Hurried)
He's moving hurriedly.
He became hurried.
They called over a higher-up for the emergency situation.
- I think the CEO came. - Yes.
I can't put it on.
Why don't you try this on?
I'll wear it carefully.
(There won't be any more size issues!)
I like it.
- There we go. - That's it.
- That's right. - It fits.
You need to wear a hat with that style.
That's the Hollywood style I want.
It looks pretty with the hat.
- Sung Hwan. - That's right.
- Sung Hwan. - He must've bought it.
- Is it the same jacket? - Sung Hwan.
(This is the Hollywood jacket.)
Hold on. You bought the jacket, but not the T-shirt...
- and the pants. - The rest of the items are old.
- You've had them. - I see.
- They go well together. - Well done.
(Staring)
Don't I look like a factory worker?
- That's the vibe. - That's the workwear style.
I had no idea.
The style is based on workwear.
- Workwear? Laborers. - Yes. The laborers of the past...
- He calls it workwear too. - I had no idea.
When I zip it up, I'm reminded of Ulsan.
An Ulsan factory.
- Ulsan. - He looks perfect.
I saw such clothes in Ulsan.
- They come outside like that. - During breaks?
- Of course. - That's a very cool style.
- That's right. - That's right.
That's a very cool style.
We'll recommend an entire outfit.
- What's your pant size? - It's 36.
- It's 36. - The owner came.
Gosh, his arms...
It's the most basic item.
I'll wear it inside.
What a pretty outfit!
- What? - Like a Hollywood star...
The colors are very different.
- Is this how I wear it? - You look very nice.
- The pants look perfect too. - Is the size okay?
I'm sucking in my stomach,
- but it's okay. - Is that so?
It's XL.
(Wearing the full set, he faces the mirror.)
The outfit suits you very well.
It looks pretty.
(Finally!)
You look much slimmer.
You're right. I can see that when I watch the video.
In autumn in Hollywood,
you might wear shorts and a white T-shirt.
It had the effortless style. The outfit looked very good on me.
The overall lengths and size...
felt comfortable for the first time in a while.
I'll get this jacket.
It would've been nice to have other items in your size.
I know. Seriously, this is my style. This is the American style.
- Please sign here. - Okay.
(Due to the body type issue, he purchases one item today.)
It's a good purchase.
- All right. - Thank you.
(He still managed to get one item with the Hollywood vibes.)
- Bye. - Have a safe trip home.
(I'll come again.)
The clothes are pretty.
(The clothes are pretty.)
Where is he going this time?
(Sung Hwan goes somewhere after buying one clothing item.)
My goodness.
(Grunting)
- What will he do with his knees? - My legs hurt.
Oh, no. Walking made me hungry.
You're lying!
Have you no conscience?
Jjamppong.
It looks delicious.
- Still, you suppressed the urge. - Yes.
- He suppressed the urge. - Yes, I did.
I'm on a diet.
Of course.
(Sung Hwan, I like your passion.)
That's the place.
That's right. That's a specialty of Itaewon.
I've only heard of it.
That's the place.
(He walks diligently and arrives at a place.)
(Big clothing)
That's it. I knew that he'd visit a plus-size clothing store.
That's right. That's a specialty of Itaewon.
I've only heard of it.
Skinny ones, take a look.
You guys won't ever go there.
- Many people are bigger than you. - There are many bigger people.
- The "Tasty Guys" cast, of course. - Yoo Min Sang,
- Kim Joon Hyun, and everyone. - Of course.
Itaewon is known for plus-size clothing.
The clothing size was regrettable at the first store I visited.
Had I lost about 15kg, the size would've been perfect.
Since I couldn't wear those clothes,
I went to a plus-size clothing store to buy some casual items.
- Hello. - Welcome.
(Looking around)
- I wonder how big they'll be. - Hello.
- Sir. - Hello.
- I just visited another store... - He's checking Sung Hwan out.
- and tried on their clothes. - He's scanning my body.
But the small size was a problem.
I won't have that problem here,
- right? - You won't have that problem.
- Gosh, my size... - Are there 5XL clothes?
As you can see, there are long-sleeve shirts,
short-sleeve shirts, jumpers, and other clothes.
Sir, I like the Hollywood style.
The effortless style you'd see on a Hollywood star...
when he comes out for a walk.
- That kind of style. - I like those clothes.
The clothes Hollywood stars might wear.
- Something like this. - Something like that.
It's huge.
(King size)
- The size is incredible. - Something like this.
- May I try this on? - Yes.
You'll be able to wear it anywhere.
I won't be able to wear this.
- It's big. It's obviously big. - This is...
It's very...
I can't believe it's so big on me.
Would there be any clothes of a slightly smaller size?
Please recommend some items to me.
You must like tight clothes.
- I like them a bit tight. - The formal and fitted clothes.
I like fitted clothes that still let me be active.
I'll show you the smallest items in the store.
- This one is nice too. - That one.
You can match it with a white T-shirt...
- and leave the buttons open. - I can leave the buttons open.
- This one. - A denim shirt.
- I think it'll be nice. - It'll be nice.
While it's pretty...
Gosh, his shoulders...
- They're insane, right? - They're insane.
The fit is a bit off.
The jacket you wore...
- in the previous store was better. - I agree.
While this store is nice, its style doesn't suit me.
Clothes with loose sleeves...
- don't look good on you. - You're right.
Your strengths are shoulders and arms.
(He tries on an item that's more fitted this time.)
Seriously,
I became much bigger after gaining about 10kg.
I can't believe I'm wearing a plus-size item.
(I feel like something is missing.)
I need clothes that are more Hollywood.
Since I'm in Itaewon, I should look for an item...
I can wear over a short-sleeve T-shirt...
- like a Hawaiian shirt. - A Hawaiian shirt.
This one looks nice. Sir,
how much is it?
- It's 35 dollars. - It's 35 dollars.
The price is reasonable.
Sir, it'll be nice on a beach.
Many people wear it...
- when they go on a vacation. - A vacation.
I'll try this item in 4XL. Is my size available?
Yes, your size is available.
Okay.
(I really hope this one suits me.)
Not bad.
It looks nice.
He has a big stomach.
Let me imagine carrying a suitcase.
Where are you from?
You should carry this bag.
- A clutch? - A clutch.
- He should carry a clutch... - A clutch.
- and wear a gold bracelet. - He should carry it like this.
Sir, how do I look?
- The style is perfect. - Do I look okay?
It looks like you're going abroad.
- I'm just missing a suitcase. - Yes.
(The owner's compliment puts him in a good mood.)
The shirt is pretty.
(He loves it.)
It's nice.
Sir, I'll get the white Hawaiian shirt.
Sir, thank you so much. I love it.
- I'll get going now. - Bye.
- Thank you. - It was a good purchase.
It was a good purchase.
I learned more about my skin and myself.
I came to love myself more...
even though it was the first day.
I also went shopping toward the end of the day.
It was nice. The items were pretty.
It wasn't about the change in my appearance.
After I was done, I thought to myself,
"I did it today."
The first day of taking care of myself went well.
I'm in a good mood.
- It was a fruitful day. - Yes.
You did well.
It shouldn't be a one-time thing.
- You should do it regularly. - Yes.
Are you doing a good job with it?
I went back one more time since that day.
It hurt so much, but I received the treatment.
I need to continue receiving treatments.
More people suffer from vitiligo than you'd think.
Vitiligo patients, let's fight on.
(Let's fight on!)
Now comes Clear-Eyed Lunatic with burning passion.
Let's watch MINHO's video.
What will he do?
It's already passionate.
Must we watch it?
Come on! We've just begun.
He'll exercise again.
(The Day of Favorites)
- The Day of Favorites? - The Day of Favorites?
- That means he'll work out. - He'll work out with someone.
See? It's a gym.
Have a nice day.
He's coming out after a workout session.
(MINHO comes out of a gym today as well.)
I began my day with a short workout session.
My goodness.
Working out is a must.
He's seriously incredible.
I had another schedule today. So I went there...
and finished working out.
I had to travel a bit far for an important appointment.
So I made sure I looked cool.
(He wears cool clothes instead of exercise clothes.)
Does he do anything other than exercising?
The sun is so bright.
Why did you wear sunglasses on the back of your head?
- Seriously. - Seriously.
- You're right. - Your eyes aren't on the back.
That's nonsense.
He made himself stylish.
He's showing the world that he's an idol.
Why are you guys picking on me...
from the very start? Seriously.
I've been curious since my last visit.
- But I want to tease you. - I've been curious.
I guess that's your charm.
Teasing him is a must.
(He goes somewhere as he shows off his charms.)
(His steps are powerful...)
(and his facial expression is excited.)
Where is he going?
Is he going to exercise?
I need to cross the road.
(Hurried)
(Hopping)
What is he doing so suddenly?
There are many people.
(He runs and arrives at a place.)
- Isn't it a yoga place? - It isn't a restaurant.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- He came. Uncle MINHO came. - Hello.
(Welcoming)
It's my favorite Korean restaurant.
It's a buffet.
You don't know what the menu will be.
The menu changes every day.
- The food items look good. - A Korean buffet.
I never get tired of it.
I go there often...
- because the amount isn't set. - That's right.
- That's nice. - I live alone,
so I can't eat home-cooked food very often.
I can have a hearty meal for eight dollars.
- What a nice deal. - There's no place like it.
I want to eat there again.
It's one of my favorite restaurants.
If the price is eight dollars, it's very cost-effective.
It's incredibly cost-effective.
You can't eat braised tofu when you live alone.
- That's right. - That's right.
You can't eat mung bean jelly.
It's impossible.
When I go there at lunchtime,
many people drink soju with the meal.
I love Korean buffets too.
- You love such restaurants. - Yes.
Celebrities like us love Korean buffets.
It's so tasty.
Celebrities like us?
I wanted to be born as the son of a Korean buffet owner.
The business would've gone under.
(Don't do that.)
That would've made you the most undutiful son.
No parent deserves that!
"Why are there no profits even though I work all day long?"
It would've been a disaster.
- I was thoughtless. - That's right.
(He goes to get food.)
My goodness.
I love that round plate.
That's it.
- It's easy to wash it. - Yes.
Today, there's a tofu dish.
Thank you for the food.
- Okay. Enjoy the food. - Okay.
Most customers left, right?
- Yes, they left. - Right? I'm glad.
- We're less busy on Friday. - I see.
Today's menu is no joke.
I haven't had braised tofu in a long while.
(It looks delicious.)
Pour the sauce over the rice.
- Make the rice soak it up. - Yes.
I tend to get every dish.
The main dish must be next to the rice.
That way, the rice soaks up the sauce.
I put other side dishes on the edge...
so that they don't get mixed up with the sauce.
(He piles up the side dishes with his own philosophy.)
He knows well. He has know-how.
Gosh, he's good at piling up food.
He's really good at it.
(Gulping)
(He hurriedly takes it to his seat.)
He's eating a lot today.
He should eat a lot.
It's so cost-effective.
(Home-style side dishes that rival home-cooked food)
- You get the soup separately. - Yes, they bring it to you.
That's so nice.
(Let's hurry up and eat.)
(Impressed)
It's budae jjigae.
Do they give you budae jjigae?
Budae jjigae.
Gosh, it's so nice.
(He warms up his stomach with budae jjigae.)
(Eating)
(He puts two spoonfuls of rice in his mouth.)
(He starts with the meat that's the main dish.)
That's a Korean buffet.
(This is it.)
(Dancing)
It's so tasty.
(Tasty food makes him dance.)
(He tries each side dish.)
I envy him because he can eat anything he wants.
His body stays beautiful no matter what he eats.
I know.
No, his body stays beautiful because he works out.
(Taking off)
He removes a fashionable item.
I hope he leaves it in the restaurant.
(Being a meanie)
I stuck it on my bag, okay?
I'm annoyed because he's too perfect.
He eats a lot,
but his body and face are beautiful.
He works out.
- That kind of jealousy is bad. - It's bad.
I'm annoyed.
(I'm jealous.)
(His perfect lunch will make anyone jealous.)
(He keeps his eyes on the food.)
- He eats food with so much gusto. - I know.
It must be because he fills his mouth.
- I'm the type to fill my mouth. - Exactly.
(Halting)
(He finished his plate.)
(Getting up)
- Will he have another plate? - Of course.
They have incredible cooking skills.
(He opens the rice cooker again.)
Just a bit.
- Just a bit. - That's right.
Just his favorite dishes.
What's this? It's so tasty.
Auntie, what's this?
- What is it? - It's dried zucchini.
- Zucchini. - Dried zucchini.
- It looks tasty. - It looks so tasty.
It's delicious.
It's hard to eat dried zucchini.
It's hard to come by.
(He resumes with a dried zucchini dish.)
(Impressed)
- He's still enjoying the food. - He eats with gusto.
I feel hungry again. I want to eat it again.
Bottoms up.
(He finishes the soup.)
It's tasty.
(He clears the second plate.)
- Thank you for the food. - Okay.
- Bye. - Bye.
(He pays himself.)
Really?
Sometimes, they do it for me. But I visit so often.
- That means he's a regular. - I'm a regular.
(10 dollars)
What?
Usually, I pay eight dollars.
But I feel like I eat a bit more than the others.
That's why I pay more at times.
I felt like I ate a lot, so I paid a few more dollars.
That's a good mindset.
How much should people pay now that he has said that?
You should pay 40 dollars.
The owner will punch in the numbers herself.
(Let's eat a lot and pay generously!)
(He pays generously out of goodness of his heart.)
- Thank you for the food. - Bye.
I'll come again.
- Okay. Come again. - Okay.
Okay.
(Lunch buffet)
(He comes outside with a toothpick in his mouth.)
He's cool.
It was a good meal.
(He walks over to a place.)
(Humming)
(Being full makes him hum.)
(Taking off)
He'll put them on now.
(After lunch, he makes himself cool again.)
(He stops...)
(at a bus station?)
(When will it come?)
Will you take a bus?
MINHO, won't people recognize you if you take a bus?
I take public transportation when I'm not working.
Most people don't look at me.
- Right. - People are on their phones.
- That's right. - People aren't...
- that interested in celebrities. - That's right.
- Cars take longer. - That's right.
You can do something when you take a bus.
That's right.
It's here.
Hello.
(He gets on the bus quickly.)
(Number 2014, Seongsu-dong to Dongdaemun History and Culture Park)
It's cool.
(MINHO sits at the very end.)
Everyone has...
a favorite spot on the bus.
- I like the very back seat. - I see.
- He looks like a college student. - Yes.
A college student, my foot.
He's old enough to be an affiliated professor.
- He's cold. - Well done.
- All right. - He's at that age.
He's 35. He's too old to be a college student.
Hyun Moo attacked Sung Hwan's video.
- KEY attacks my video. - That's right.
All of us have a role.
- That's right. - All of you have a role.
- That's right. - That's right.
- I only attack you. - I'm waiting...
for your video.
Seriously.
"I only attack you."
(Looking here...)
(and there)
(He studies the world outside the window.)
The view you get on a bus is very nice,
so I enjoy it often.
You meet many new people...
in that small space.
I tend to watch people...
come and go.
It's fun to observe people.
I look at the scenery...
as well as people inside the bus.
I enjoy my daily life that way.
It's a therapeutic time for me.
It's the charm of a bus.
There was a memorable scene from that day.
A high school couple got on.
The girl sat down...
and the boy looked at her like this.
- My heart fluttered so much. - Oh, my.
Seriously.
Looking at them made me think, "This is heart-fluttering."
My heart fluttered for the first time in a while.
I see.
If you're jealous, that means you're a middle-aged man.
I've become a middle-aged man.
(He watches the world from the back of the bus.)
(He enjoys the view with excitement in his heart.)
He's traveling far.
(Pressing the bell)
I press the bell...
- faster than anyone. - Why?
I want to press it.
- You want to be the first to press it. - I want to be the first.
Babies want to press the elevator button...
- with the same mindset. - That's right.
Do you get competitive about it?
- A child might cry. - I want to do it for some reason.
(He checks the route sign again.)
He's transferring to another bus.
He obviously takes the bus often.
- He knows the route. - Yes.
I see.
(It's here.)
(He enters the bus that's full of people again.)
(This time as well, he checks out the scenery.)
(Hyehwa-dong Rotary)
- Hyehwa-dong? - What?
- Daehangno? - Isn't that Daehangno?
I'm here.
Perilla leaf tteokbokki is tasty.
- It's tasty. - There are many good restaurants.
(MINHO arrives at a place by bus.)
The weather is nice.
They're having an event.
This is the avenue of youth,
Daehangno, Hyehwa.
- Something is happening there. - I began my career there.
I built stages.
I like that atmosphere of Daehangno.
- I haven't gone there in a while. - I know.
I've liked Daehangno a lot...
since my 20s.
(Many performances have taken place in this neighborhood.)
- In small theaters, - Cultwo Hall.
(In small theaters)
a new world is always born.
I think the neighborhood is full of excitement.
That's right.
When I visit the neighborhood during my time off,
I receive a lot of good energy.
So, I think it's a great place.
Everyone has such places outside of home.
To me, Daehangno is that kind of place.
(He enjoys Daehangno in a relaxed way.)
Will he watch a play?
(He heads over to a place without a word.)
(He follows the winding alleys as if he was used to them.)
He knows the nooks and crannies.
- Hello. - Hello.
Isn't it a curry place?
I like atmospheric places.
I went straight over...
to the atmospheric cafe I liked the most.
- A cafe. - It looks nice.
May I take your order?
I'll get ssanghwatang.
- Do they sell ssanghwatang? - Yes, I'll get one.
I'll also get one iced filter coffee.
When we are ready, we will call you by name or nickname.
- What should we call you by? - Choi MINHO.
- Choi MINHO? Thank you. - Thank you.
- You should've gone with SHINee. - Right.
"Fiery Charisma, MINHO." You should've gone with that.
- "Fiery Charisma, MINHO." - "Fiery Charisma, MINHO."
I should've gone with that.
- Fiery Charisma, MINHO. - That would've been perfect.
- Right. - You should've gone with that.
- What a bummer. - You should've gone with that.
- I'll do that next time. - Definitely.
That place is usually crowded.
- I went when it wasn't busy. - Right.
Choi MINHO.
"Fiery Charisma, MINHO."
"Fiery Charisma."
- Gosh, I missed that chance. - Right.
- I'll make sure to do that. - Right.
It's pretty. It feels like a chairman's house.
(A relaxed time at his favorite cafe)
(He starts by taking a sip of the warm ssanghwacha.)
You're not having the egg yolk.
They don't have that there.
(Satisfied)
(He drinks the iced coffee as well.)
(Refreshed)
What is that?
- It's a cake. - Gosh. That looks good.
It looks like a dumpling.
It's filled with chestnut.
- Chestnut? - That must be good.
- That was why it looked like one. - That must be good.
That looks good.
- It's like Mont Blanc. - Right.
He's able to eat freely as he works out.
I got really surprised today.
I checked my body composition and I got really surprised.
- Why? - Why?
- I'm not on a diet, - Right.
But I had four percent of body fat.
- What? - I got so surprised.
I got so surprised.
Things might get serious for you!
That's the body that bodybuilders have before competitions.
- Right. - I got surprised today.
- He just has his shell. - How often do you work out?
I was expecting 6 or 7 percent.
I've never seen anyone at four percent.
He was always a nothingburger.
He's trying to bring him down no matter what.
- Gosh. - He was always hollow...
- and had nothing inside. - A nothingburger.
It's good.
How is that possible?
Having just that...
- would increase it by one percent. - Exactly.
We would gain three percent...
as we have terrible basal metabolic rates.
(The dessert disappears in a flash.)
MINHO's always been someone who never gains weight easily.
- Right. - Ever since he was young.
I'm so jealous.
It's healthy and good for my throat as it's warm.
(He also clears up the coffee without leaving any.)
All of us love coffee so much.
Right.
It was neatly finished.
Four percent of body fat.
It's 4pm.
It's 4pm, so...
I have a lot of time.
Okay. Let's get going.
- Thank you. Goodbye. - I'll come again.
Thank you.
It smells nice.
(He hums as he walks.)
I'm going to kill you if you work out again.
(I'm going to kill you if you work out again.)
(He's walking up?)
- There's a place like this? - Where is he going?
How far up is he going?
(He walks uphill for quite a while.)
(He even walks up stairs.)
The weather is great.
Is he hiking?
Isn't that Naksan Park?
(Naksan Park)
It's my favorite atmospheric place.
- Right. - It appeared in...
"KPop Demon Hunters" and it became really popular.
(It appeared as a background of a popular film.)
(Naksan Park became a popular spot for people around the world.)
(The night view is great.)
If I go up at night,
Mount Bukhan can't be seen.
That is why I prefer going up during the day than at night.
Right. You can see a lot more.
This is my choice for a perfect day.
Choi MINHO's Choice.
(Appalled)
I got goosebumps all over.
I can't say a thing.
I should just stay silent.
- I should stay silent. - Gosh.
This is why I love MINHO.
(Charming MINHO is someone you want to tease all the time.)
(He walks into...)
(a restroom?)
Why is he going to the restroom?
This was why I brought my clothes.
- I knew it. - No way.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(He appears in his workout clothes!)
I was right, wasn't I?
You're really something.
I got so surprised.
How do you know me so well?
(He enters the mountain.)
(Breathing)
Let's go!
- Gosh, he's running! - What?
I always have a T-shirt and shorts in my bag.
I was just going to walk up my favorite spot,
but my eyes suddenly opened wide with a burst of energy.
I needed to do something about it.
(That is why he's sprinting uphill full of excitement.)
(Excited)
Gosh, he's that excited?
- He really started working out. - Right.
What now?
I must watch out for my knees when I'm going downhill.
(He keeps his pace even while going downhill.)
Gosh.
You have to be more careful when going down.
Right.
Gosh, I would've already collapsed.
No way!
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Gosh, I'm sweating.
That's just...
(He runs back up the stairs he ran down.)
(Light)
It has begun. Uphill!
Let's go!
- "Uphill." - Why go down to go back up?
There's no time for any body fat to be made.
Right.
I think four percent of body fat is still a lot for him.
Right. He should have around two percent.
Does doing that make you feel better?
My eyes opened wide after having the ssanghwatang.
You should see a doctor.
The ssanghwatang might be the problem.
I can't say anything!
One, two.
A bit more!
I'm almost there!
Going uphill is tough.
He has to run up.
He would run around the country with four burgers.
(He quickly reaches the peak!)
I should try some of that ssanghwatang.
(Panting)
I have arrived.
Gosh, that's great.
You run to feel that.
Right. I ran up there to feel that.
Do you understand the joy you feel at that moment?
I do.
It feels annoying when you run out of breath.
But as for sportsmen like us...
- "Sportsmen like us." - Well,
we enjoy that pleasure felt...
- when our heart rate returns. - You enjoy that?
- Do you understand that? - Not at all.
I'm just like you.
- Right? - We're finally on the same page.
That was perfect.
(Feeling refreshed)
Let's go, SHINee!
Oh, hello! Thank you!
The older ladies really like him.
He looks handsome.
It's tough to go uphill.
The slope was higher up than I thought,
so it was perfect for a workout.
(Hold on.)
I should hide it.
- Is he running in earnest? - No way.
- Why hide your bag? - He's hiding his bag.
- He's going to run in earnest. - Where is he going now?
- He put his bag down. - Where is he going now?
Great.
(His body feels much lighter.)
It's less than 1km.
I'll go for 5 minutes and 30 seconds.
He's going for 5 minutes and 30 seconds.
- An uphill course? - Gosh.
- Does that make sense? - That's impossible.
There are quite a lot of steps.
Going up those stairs at that pace doesn't make sense.
Get ready.
(He starts timing his record!)
Why do this?
I wanted to check my record.
(He sprints uphill!)
Gosh, it's so high up.
Sean didn't contact you, right?
- He didn't. - He's scared to contact you.
(His fiery pace doesn't slow down even while going uphill.)
You should be enjoying the view. Why run around?
(Running past)
(He arrives at his destination in a flash.)
(He returns to the starting point.)
Gosh. Did he make it before 5 minutes and 30 seconds?
- I think he made it. - I think he made it.
With that pace.
(That was a clean run.)
The lunatic with clear eyes.
(What's my record?)
I recorded 2 minutes and 13 seconds.
How long was the course?
- It was less than 1km. - But it was an uphill course.
- It looked really high up. - Right.
After hearing his record, I think he can run a sub-three marathon.
- Definitely. - He can do that.
- He can run a sub-three marathon. - What exactly is that?
It's running a full course in three hours.
I heard that was a dream record for marathoners.
It's a dream record...
for regular runners. I think he can do that.
(I did it.)
My bag!
- Please be stolen. - His bag should be missing.
- That will be entertainment. - That would make me so happy.
Unfortunately, our country is safe.
Right. We live in a safe country.
No one would take that even after three days.
- Right. - We live in a great country.
It's still there.
(He starts running after getting back his bag.)
- No way. - No. You don't have to worry.
It's a chance to lie down!
(Breathing out)
(He gets up after a good stretch.)
This feels amazing.
(He relaxedly enjoys his favorite scenery.)
It's my favorite bench.
- If I sit there, - It seems that way.
I can see Mount Bukhan well.
(Getting up)
(He quickly moves after seeing Mount Bukhan.)
This feels great.
(He comes back down to where he started.)
(He enters the restroom again.)
He must smell terrible.
"He must smell terrible."
(He gets changed into clothes that aren't smelly.)
- I had a towel, - I bet.
- so I wiped myself with it. - Let's go.
There are good towels these days.
- Right. - Right.
The ssanghwatang and coffee all went away with my sweat.
- Where will he go now? - Will he run back home?
(The place he walks into)
Hello.
(A bakery filled with the smell of bread)
(It smells sweet all around.)
Gosh, this place looks good.
This place has great bread.
- The matcha one looks good. - Right.
This is my favorite bakery.
I would like to get two pieces of Salt Bread.
- One Palmier Carre... - Palmier Carre?
And one Salt.
- Right. - Will you get four in total?
No. I'll be getting more.
Gosh, he's getting a lot.
I'll get two pieces of Salt.
Two pieces of Salt Bread and two pieces of Salt.
I'll get two Palmier Carres as well.
Also...
(He gets a generous amount of bread.)
One Almond...
and the Ham and Cheese.
He must be going somewhere.
- It must be for his trainers. - Right.
- As a gift? - Right.
He only meets his trainers.
- I barely get to see him either. - They're the only ones he meets.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Goodbye. - Thank you. Enjoy the bread.
- He's not eating them. - He must be eating at home.
(Where is he heading to with both hands full of snacks?)
Where is he going?
He got some coffee as well.
Right.
I figured it out.
He must be meeting someone.
Right.
(Hall 3 Ticket Office)
Is he watching a performance?
He's been watching a lot of plays these days.
I see.
(He opens the door with an excited heart.)
(He arrives at the theater.)
This is a theater in Daehangno...
where I am currently performing.
- So this is before the performance? - Right.
(The stage that is ready for the performance...)
(is filled with items that build up the setting.)
I performed for around two weeks.
- At that time? - Right.
Hi.
You're here early.
Come down and have some of this.
He brought it for the staff.
(He goes backstage naturally.)
- Hello! - Hey, MINHO!
- I've come with both hands full! - Gosh!
- Gosh. - I brought bread and drinks.
- Gosh. - It's Lee Sang Yun!
- Byoung Cheol! - It's Byoung Cheol.
Mr. Catastrophe!
(Mr. Catastrophe)
(Actor Kim Byoung Cheol)
(Soft charisma in mildness)
(Actor Lee Sang Yun)
Kim Byoung Cheol...
and Lee Sang Yun.
Since I'm the youngest,
they treat me well with whatever I do.
They listen to everything I say.
I thought that I should do well as the youngest.
That was why I went to support them.
(I went to support my seniors.)
Sang Yun and I are doubles.
Byoung Cheol is a different character.
Was Byoung Cheol double cast as well?
Yes. Byoung Cheol...
is double cast with Park Geun Hyung.
- Park Geun Hyung? - Yes.
I brought three for you.
- Awesome. - Choose from them.
I didn't feel like having coffee for some reason.
- Really? - I must've known you were coming.
Fortunately, he didn't have any coffee.
- That was a relief. - Right.
Coffee for you.
(The youngest delivers coffee to everyone.)
Byoung Cheol.
I got something for you.
You should brush your teeth again.
(Thank you, Youngest.)
I had this and it was really good.
I thought it would be perfect for Byoung Cheol.
- I bought ssanghwatang. - I was going to mention that!
I was going to ask if it was ssanghwatang.
It's good for the throat.
- It suits Byoung Cheol. - Right.
Did you not work out today?
I worked out during the day.
What did you do today?
Today,
I did something like CrossFit.
- It's the circuit? - Right. I did that slightly.
And I did two laps in Naksan Park.
I went back and forth.
That was a brief workout?
- Right. - That was a brief workout?
- Gosh, you brought bread as well. - Right.
He brought us bread as well.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
- Do you have your own? - He's good to the older guys.
Right.
- He knows how to be loved. - They all took great care of me...
during rehearsals.
They take good care of you because you treat them so well.
They take good care of you because you do well.
What did you do in the morning?
Today,
I was with KSOC...
as I became an ambassador.
(I became an ambassador.)
I went to the appointment ceremony.
- That suits you perfectly. - He's an athlete now.
He became an ambassador of KSOC today.
Congratulations, MINHO.
He doesn't even look surprised.
He knows him too well.
Will you get paid regularly?
- No. It's just an honorary title. - "Paid regularly?"
- An honorary title. - Right.
I will be sharing with everyone that exercising is great.
I see.
Just like how you work out before getting on stage.
- He works out really hard. - He's intense.
I got so surprised. He kept doing the plank.
I got really surprised.
You three all look very close. Were you always that close?
Sang Yun made a great effort...
to make all of us get along.
Byoung Cheol was actually a very shy person,
but we got very close as he broke the ice for us.
- Byoung Cheol. - Have this, Byoung Cheol.
I bought ssanghwatang for you.
You seemed to have a bad throat for a while.
He's really good to the older ones.
Right. He knows how to be loved.
- Really? - Yes.
(Touched)
I bought it for you.
(Acting cute)
It's healthy and is good for your throat.
You should stay healthy.
- Right. - Right.
MINHO got it for you.
You're always smiling.
- Byoung Cheol lives alone. - Right.
- You also live alone. - Right.
We all live alone.
- Right. - Right.
- Really? - They are future...
- Rainbow Club members. - Gosh.
- I'm curious about your day. - Same here.
- I'm curious about him too. - Me too.
How do you eat at home?
- I'm curious. - Right.
I wonder how you eat meat at home.
- Meat? - Does he like meat?
- How? - Yes.
I buy minced meat and stir-fry it.
- He's on a diet? - Well,
he does have carbs,
- but he only has a little. - He controls what he eats.
He usually has protein-based meals.
Gosh.
But you bought eight pieces of bread?
That was why I bought...
the one with bacon for him.
The Ham and Cheese.
- Since it has protein. - Right.
- I see. - I see.
This is how amazing he is.
I worked in a film called "GP506" with him in 2005.
You were in that?
- I didn't see you in that. - I was a soldier.
He was a fellow soldier.
He looks just the same as before.
Nothing has changed about him.
He must be an expert in self-management.
Only meat?
There are times when I have it with rice.
What about the sauce?
- Sauce? I have it with salt. - Gosh.
- That's amazing. - Salt and pepper.
- He takes great care of himself. - Right.
I do have ketchup as well.
You eat suyuk often as well, right?
Right.
I have boiled meat as well.
- He must like all kinds of meat. - Right.
- He's a meat lover. - A meat lover.
Is this the one with bacon?
Yes.
(Taking a big bite thanks to the youngest)
He's even eating the bread?
He usually doesn't eat bread, but ate it since I got it for him.
(Feeling proud)
I was worried about your throat.
I think...
the vocal cords need to be stretched as well.
(The vocal cords need to be stretched as well.)
I found out that there was a way...
to warm up your vocal cords with a straw.
- It felt quite effective. - Really?
(Vocal cord stretching with a straw)
We have straws, so we can give it a try.
I'm so curious.
(Eyes fixed on Byoung Cheol out of curiosity)
I don't know it quite well as I looked it up online yesterday.
- Here. - We can be your students.
Your student is ready.
- I'll give it a try. - Okay.
(The straw is bitten slightly.)
(Making sounds with his throat)
(A method of relaxing the vocal cords with vibration)
(Intrigued)
This is how it's done.
- To know if it's working, - Yes?
You should block your nose.
It's working...
if the sound doesn't change when you block your nose.
It's not working if the sound changes.
(Pressing together)
This is a method...
that Kim Bum Soo actually uses.
It helps vibrate the vocal cords effectively...
and it clears your throat very quickly.
ENT doctors tell you something similar.
It's along those lines.
Like this.
- After blocking the nose? - Right.
The lips are gathered.
They say that helps with the vocal cords.
I think it's the same principle.
- I think it cleared my throat. - Really?
- I think it cleared my throat. - It sounds nice.
(It sounds nice.)
- It sounds much better. - It really did.
- I sound better. - Right.
I got so surprised as it really helped.
Nice!
So this was how these three got close.
I've been having this thought a lot.
"Where do I get my energy?"
With this thought in mind,
Daehangno is a place where I can rest,
but it's also a place where I receive a lot of energy.
(A place where he can work out)
(A place filled with affection)
Daehangno was the place...
that I have always dreamed of.
It's a place that charges me up.
(Eyes shining brightly)
(A day spent at the place he loves...)
(with the people he loves)
(This is why he is filled with joy.)
- MINHO got charged up. - Right.
Good luck!
(Charged up 100 percent!)
You were so sweet as the youngest there.
- You're the youngest here as well. - Right.
- Right. - Right.
But why can't we see that kind of energy from you here?
I only received love there.
We give you love as well.
It's just given in a different way.
- It's a different form of love. - No. It's completely different!
- What do you mean it's different? - It's different.
They treated me like a baby,
but you guys kept throwing punches at me.
(As soon as he came)
Is there anything else he does besides working out?
(A lot of expressions of love)
This love feels great as well, doesn't it?
- Well, I guess so, but... - We don't want you to turn bad.
- It's all for your good. - Right.
- It's all for your good. - We didn't say anything bad.
You're the one who feels that way.
- Right. - We don't want to butter you up.
(Thank you for your overwhelming love.)
(Next episode)
Through I Live Alone...
(Including variety shows, )
(Kian84 also made himself known for his running.)
(But he looks full of concern from behind?)
(I can't get myself to draw.)
(Gosh, this is so exhausting.)
I might be getting ambitious.
(Drawing isn't fun any more.)
No!
Gosh!
(Something has gone wrong.)
(He came to this place with a heavy heart.)
Have you been doing well?
The handsome art major.
(Choong Jae's workroom)
(I think it's tough as I feel so ambitious.)
(That's a good thing!)
(That means you have a lot you can do.)
(You're amazing.)
(Choong Jae's heart shines.)
(It feels like it's clearing him up as well.)
Chimchakman.
(This is Chimchakman's office.)
(Help me solve my struggles.)
(Get it out of your life.)
I don't have anything to say.
(You have to compromise!)
(Go with performance art!)
(Get paint on your feet!)
That's art.
(A spectacular method of solving his struggles)
It feels great to hear those things from him.
(Heart Retouch)
(There's another artist that is torn.)
(Opening)
(I wanted to get done with my album perfectly within this year.)
(Over 160 songs were written, )
(but they were never finished.)
(I need a planned life as well.)
(He came up with his own daily plan.)
(My lizards!)
(For his new family members, the lizards)
(After working hard to take care of the sand and temperature, )
(he fulfills his first schedule.)
(This is what the cool guy will do next.)
(Cleaning up the fridge in order)
(I just have to eat now.)
(What?)
(I have to eat within 10 minutes.)
(What? Already?)
(There is no time.)
(Let's move on to the next schedule quickly.)
(Hey!)
(Come on, Siru!)
(What's wrong?)
(Thanks to the disrupter, )
(things don't go according to his plan.)
(Moving here...)
(and there)
(A guest has arrived on top of that?)
(The laundry is done as well.)
(Flustered)
(I'm a planner.)
This can't be happening.
(First Plan Struggles)